

Ioannis Chionidis

Date of birth: 14/12/1996
Nationality: Greek

CONTACT

M. Karakosti 159132 Veroia, Greece (Home)

giannhschionidhs@gmail.com

(+30) 6949989387

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/giannis-chionidis-7b4078226/

https://github.com/gianxion (GitH ub)

ABOUT ME

Computer Engineering graduate. A multi-

talented individual with expertise in web development and networks.

In my most recent role, I oversaw and troubleshooted the consulting company's networks. In addition, I offered firms system administration services, equipment installation, and custom support. Additionally, I have experimented with web applications.

I have a strong desire to increase my technological expertise by learning and utilizing new tech logies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

20/03/2024 - 25/07/2024 Veroia, Greece

IT / Customer Service SEMANTIC

Installation and Configuration of equipment for Businesses Network Configurations/Troubleshooting Customer Support

27/11/2023 - 20/03/2024 Veroia, Greece

ERP Customer Service / Consultant SEMANTIC

SQL Configuration Software Installation / Troubleshooting ERP Configuration

17/03/2023 - 19/10/2023 Veroia, Greece

IT Technician MTEL

Customer Support Studied Web Applications on Js HTML CSS MongoDB Equipment Installation / Configuration for Networks

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2014 - 09/06/2022 Kastoria, Greece

Bachelor's degree, Software Engineer, General Technological Education Institute of Western Macedonia

Address Fourka, 52100, Kastoria, Greece | Website https://cs.uowm.gr

PROJECTS

Packing List React

React App for Making a responsive list of items for any kind of use.

Links https://github.com/gianxion/PackingListTutorial https://packing-list-tutorial.vercel.app

Trivia Questions React

Mini Game of Trivia Questions with React and Codux.

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} Links & https://github.com/gianxion/React-Trivia-Questions & https://react-trivia-questions-24e4.vercel.app & https://react-trivia-questions-24e4.vercel.app & https://github.com/gianxion/React-Trivia-Questions & https://react-trivia-questions-24e4.vercel.app &$

React Clothing E-Shop

A React app for displaying and selling clothes. JS MongoDB

Link https://github.com/gianxion/ReactClothingShop

Monster Energy Drink Page

An online shop for displaying and selling Monster Energy drinks made mainly with (JS, HTM CSS), MongoDB, Express , NodeJs and Strapi.

 ${\color{red}\textbf{Link}}~\underline{\textbf{https://github.com/gianxion/MonsterEnergyDrink}}$

Fractal Explore with .NET (Thesis)

.NET application for local use. Shows fractals on screen and allows user to explore them "infinitely".

Link https://github.com/gianxion/Fractal-Explorer-In-.Net